好了  我们要赶快想辙打发掉老爸
All right, we have got to think fast.
来参加丽芙鲁尼住宅游的妹子们
The girls coming for the Liv Rooney residential tour
随时都会到
Will be here any minute,
而老爹表现得像他是这儿的老大一样
And dad is acting like he owns the place.
他貌似确实是啊
He sort of does.
我们需要一个能让
We need a project
老爹忙得不可开交的计划
That will keep dad busy.
你干啥呢  你知道老妈对垃圾粉碎机的严格规定的
You know how strict mom is about what goes in the disposal.
这么做会弄坏它的
That's gonna break it.
原来如此  快塞进去
Shove it in.
全都塞进去
Shove it all in.
爸 垃圾粉碎机好像坏了
Dad! something's wrong with the disposal.
快来修好它啊
You need to fix it.
这太妙了
This is perfect.
你知道吧  老爹一直是干什么事
You know how dad takes forever
都干到不知猴年马月的
To do pretty much anything.
你做了什么啊
What'd you do?
你知道老妈对垃圾粉碎机的严格规定的
You know how strict your mom is about what goes in the disposal.
这下好了
Yep.
这堵得死死的
It's jammed up real good.
但你还是能修好的  对不  爹地
You can fix it, though-- right, dad?
当然能了  我们的爸爸是个铁血真男儿啊
Of course he can. our father's a man's man.
他什么都能修好的
He can fix anything.
说对了  看来皮特叔叔要施展
Yeah, looks like it's time for pete
通管子的老身手了
To get his old plumber on.
欢迎光临 丽芙的粉丝们
Greetings, lovers of liv
和喜欢鲁尼家的人们
And all things rooney.
欢迎来到
Welcome
丽芙·鲁尼住宅游
To the Liv Rooney residential tour.
和礼品店
And gift shop.
我们必须要保持警惕  别打搅了
We must be very careful not to disturb
住宅里的其他成员
Any of the other residents.
来起步走
And we're walking.
继续向前走
这赚钱简直是易如反
It's like taking candy from a--
亚蒂
Artie.